[♪ opening theme song playing]
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[Yuru sighs]
[YURU] You've got one of those
smoke signal things, right?
[JIN] Hm?
The device that lets you talk
to people far away.
I saw you were using it earlier.
Oh, you mean my smartphone.
You're gonna tell Asa
to come here.
I just want to talk,
that's all.
All that you wanna do is talk?
Yeah, I figured he'd be
telling us to hand her over,
-"or else."
-Why settle for a simple chat?
Surely Higashi Village
wants both twins.
But that's not why I'm here.
I came on my own,
for my own reasons.
All right,
then let's continue this
at the Kagemori manor.
Asa has been wanting
to see you, too,
and you can talk there.
Only a fool would walk
willingly into a bear's den.
Have her come here.
And stop acting like
this is a negotiation
because it really isn't.
Hey, kid, tell you what.
Why don't you at least
let us see what we can do
about that wound you gave him?
He could bleed out.
I made sure it wasn't
deep enough to kill him.
But very well.
You kept it shallow on purpose?
Jin, isn't it?
You trapped me, but that's it.
I didn't sense bloodlust
in you.
[JIN] Hm.
[YURU] If you had
wanted to kill me,
things would have
turned out much differently.
[HARUO] You'd think
mountain folk would be peaceful.
But this kid's terrifying.
[YURU] It's true.
If he had wanted me dead,
he would have seen to it
with that first attack.
[RIGHT] The fish belong
to the spectacled one.
And the hare and tortoise
answer to the rumpled youth.
There's another pair somewhere,
though they have yet
to show themselves.
Yours, I assume?
Yeah. Those two would be mine.
They aren't far.
And yet they didn't aid you
in the fight?
Are they not suited
to combat, then?
Oh, suitability
is not the issue.
[ALL] Hmm?
It's just, they're too big
to fit in here.
If you want, though,
-I could make them try.
-[Yuru whimpers]
I fear bringing Asa here
is out of the question.
But if you'll let us
take you back with us
to the Kagemori manor,
no harm will come to you.
You have my word on that.
Killing you isn't my objective.
You just said as much yourself.
[Yuru breathes uneasily]
[YURU] The hare and tortoise,
plus whatever that is.
Left and Right
might be outmatched.
[YURU] Fine, I'll go
to this manor of yours.
But I want Left and Right
to be treated
with respect while we're there.
And they will be.
You're coming as our guests,
not our prisoners.
[YURU] Then let's stop talking
and move.
Take us to Asa.
[JIN] Actually, we need
to clean up a bit first.
Ai, my dear, think you can
handle this for us?
[Ai growls]
As usual, Scavenger makes
a mess wherever they go.
You mean the fish?
[JIN] Scavenger.
Nature's janitors.
Ai will eat whatever I ask.
Makoto stores those items
and summons them.
I regularly feed them things
that might come in handy,
so I'm prepared
in any situation.
Though, since they're janitors,
I sometimes feed them trash
the world's better off without.
They're quite convenient.
It makes security a breeze, too,
no matter what gear I've got.
I could carry enough
for a hit or a hijacking,
and no one would have a clue.
That was a lot of words
that don't make sense to me,
but I get your daemons
are useful.
[LEFT] And your daemons?
Uh, mine?
The tortoise to start.
How many kan is it?
[HARUO] Kan? Right.
How many kilograms
is that again?
Not that it matters,
'cause I've never actually
weighed them.
But I can tell you,
this isn't
the heaviest they get.
I require more training
before our next encounter.
[gasps]
She is one serious fighter!
[BUNBUN] Hm?
[Right grunts softly]
[Bunbun grunts]
[Right grunts]
Yuru, are you any good
at rabbit hunting?
Sure am. I like to catch them
with snares.
Once they're skinned,
they make good broth.
Barbarian!
Can daemons be eaten?
Hypothetically, I mean.
Uh, hello?
Is somebody in there?
Oh, good! Security.
We can use some help here.
We're not sure
what may have caused it,
but the lights just went out
all of a sudden.
Hmm... Uh?
What happened to them?
They're not just off.
They're broken.
[HARUO]
Maybe they short-circuited.
We heard some crackling,
and it freaked us out a bit.
[SECURITY] I see.
Fortunately, the lights
are still on in the stairwell.
You can exit through here.
[ALL] 'Kay...
We appreciate it.
Thank you!
[phone vibrating]
[Asa grunts softly]
[Asa groans softly]
[Asa gasps]
Gabby! Gabby! Gabby!
What? We under attack?
[ASA] No, look!
Jin is bringing my brother here.
[GABBY] Seriously?
That dude works fast.
I'm not ready, though!
What am I going to wear?
Uh, I don't know, clothes?
Does it matter?
[JIN] It's Jin.
Sorry to be calling so late.
I've settled things
with the brother.
That's right.
I have him in the car
with me right now.
We're on our way
to the manor as we speak.
[YURU] How long is this cave?
Yeah? Nice work.
I'm impressed.
Can you keep him there a while,
at least until I make it back?
[JIN] That depends.
Where are you, sir?
[chuckles] At a hot spring.
[GONZO] Thought I'd get
an after-work soak in,
but this is more important.
I'll go and head that way
right now.
-You'd all better be nice...
-[camera clicks]
...to young Yuru.
♪
Here we are.
The Kagemori clan home.
♪
[RIGHT] We were
to understand the Kagemoris
had a goodly number
of Daemon Wielders.
Yet I sense none of my kind.
There are plenty of them around.
We're just not
in the VIP area yet.
-[LEFT] VIP?
-[JIN] Limited access.
We'll be crossing the barrier
in a moment.
[Yuru grunts uneasily]
-Yes.
-Incredible.
[RIGHT] Daemons everywhere.
So many I can't even count
the number of pairs.
-[Gabriel grumbles]
-Hm?
Jin is pulling up into the drive
with your brother.
Now?
You wanna go with me
to greet him?
He put literal holes in my body,
so I'm gonna pass
on that invite, thanks.
Every step
still reminds me of him.
Okay. Wish me luck.
[GABBY] Go get him, girl!
I'm gonna get some sleep.
[Jiro grunts softly]
[DERA] Is that one
enormous building?
[HANA] Or a giant plot of land?
[Kotetsu grunts]
[HANA AND DERA] Hm?
[both groaning]
[HANA] Oh!
Did he get himself captured?
[DERA] Wouldn't have
thought that was possible
with Left and Right
guarding him.
Well, nothin' for it.
I'll go rescue our wayward son
from whatever trouble he's in.
[HANA] Want me to drive you?
[DERA] Nah, they don't know
we're associated yet.
Might as well keep it that way.
I'll just catch a cab.
And how will you get home?
[DERA] By train.
Yuru can learn about the joys
of public transportation.
[door opens, closes]
[YURU] What a huge entryway!
[RIGHT] Like a castle
upon the plains.
[ASUMA] Out burning
the midnight oil?
Ever the hard worker, Jin.
[HARUO] Asuma, how are you?
[JIN] Why are you out so late?
I heard that the other twin
would be arriving soon,
so I came to extend a greeting.
I don't believe you were
among the people I told.
[Asuma chuckles]
I have quite excellent hearing.
Oh, my!
You're injured.
It's nothing the doc
can't fix up for me.
Then I presume you got
in a fight with them?
Oh, what beautiful daemons!
And you, my friend,
are Asa's brother?
[Asuma chuckles]
I'm Asuma Kagemori.
At your service.
[Asa panting] Are you here?
It is you.
You're alive?
You're not dead?
[YURU] Who greets
someone like that?
Can I please give you a hug?
[YURU] Not so fast!
[Asa cries] Sorry, I don't know
how close we should be.
Neither do I.
I didn't come here
hoping to repair old bonds.
I'm here to get some
answers out of you.
You can ask me anything.
Then once we're done,
can I hug you?
[YURU] I said no!
[ASA] Oh! Oh, my gosh.
You grew up into such a badass!
Look, forget me.
Worry about this guy.
Whoa! You need to get
to the infirmary!
His injury gives us
the perfect excuse.
Why don't I take you on
a little tour around the manor?
[ASA] Oh, I didn't
see you there, Asuma.
Wow. Quite the tunnel vision
for your big brother.
I invited Yuru here,
so I'll be seeing to his stay.
You have no business
with our guest.
Very well, then.
Welcome. Please,
treat this place like home.
Akio, you're on guard
outside the barrier.
Let no one in.
Sir.
[JIN] As for you,
as long as you're at the manor,
I want you close to me.
Can't have you getting lost.
♪
[SAKURAZAWA] Oh, yeah.
That one's gonna need
some stitches.
Wait. You're kidding!
A billhook?
Straight to the calf.
[SAKURAZAWA] I was wondering
what was urgent enough
to wake me up so late.
Can't believe you got caught
by some kid with a machete.
-Teenagers are scary these days.
-[keyboard tapping]
Well, most teenagers
aren't carrying hunting weapons,
you know?
Seriously? What kind of kid
doesn't have a billhook or two?
Absolutely.
[HARUO] Twin barbarians!
Hey, doc, I'm done
with Asa's blood.
I brought it back for you.
[SAKURAZAWA] Don't make a habit
of carrying that stuff.
-It's unsanitary.
-[Yuru gasps]
Almost forgot!
What kind of fiend
would draw blood
from a young lady like that?
It was my idea for Jin
to take my blood,
so try not to judge him for it.
Modern medicine's crazy.
Because of it,
we can bleed someone
without cutting a single vein.
[YURU] Really?
What kind of sorcery--
[JIN] Her blood
was drawn safely.
We did it in this infirmary.
[SAKURAZAWA]
We use this. It's harmless.
[ASA] If a doctor's skilled,
then you don't feel anything.
[YURU] This heinous practice
is medicine?
[HARUO]
Didn't he cut open Jin's leg?
This is where he draws the line?
He's got some messed up morals.
The Kagemori clan gives me food
and keeps me safe
inside their walls,
so a little blood felt like
the least I could give back.
Would it be okay for me
to hug you now?
[grunts] No way!
I still can't get over
how big you are!
The Asa I know is tiny
and cute
and couldn't hurt a fly!
Aw, don't worry.
You'll grow bigger too
if you keep eating the food
they have down here!
I don't like it. Too salty.
Oh, you think?
[YURU] And too heavily seasoned!
Maybe I'm just used to it
after living down here
for so long.
The rice here is great!
I'll grant you that.
Hold on. I didn't come here
to talk about food.
[ASA] Right! You said you have
-questions for me, yeah?
-[YURU] Yeah.
[ASA] And after I answer,
then can I hug you?
[YURU] Gotta hand it to you,
you sure don't give up!
[HARUO] They're pretty in sync.
Must be a twin thing.
You're gonna tell me
where Mom and Dad are.
[Asa gasps softly]
Let me see them.
You fled the village together,
didn't you?
-Then...
-[ASA] They're not here.
Where are they?
I wish I knew.
[Yuru gasps softly]
[ASA] Unfortunately,
they're missing.
♪
[JIN] How much
should I tell him?
All of it.
After everything,
I refuse to lie to my brother.
[Jin sighs softly]
Your parents didn't have
an easy go of things
after they fled the village.
So they came to the Kagemoris
seeking protection.
Took a while to settle in.
But once they finally had,
they decided to pay a visit
to your mother's home.
That's right.
My mother told me she was born
in a place down the mountain.
She said she wanted
to take me there.
[JIN] Your mother's from a place
called Okinawa.
[ASA] It's an island
far to the south
of the mainland.
You would need a boat
or a plane to get there.
[YURU] What's a "plane?"
We called them "dragons"
in the village.
[YURU] You mean
those are vehicles?
[ASA] Yes, and they carry
more than a hundred people.
Mom had family here,
and as far as they knew,
she went missing
in some mountains in Tohoku.
She was hoping
to show her own parents
that she was still alive,
so she left me here
in the care of the Kagemoris.
They boarded the plane
to Okinawa, but didn't land.
They're gone.
[Yuru gasps softly]
[YURU] The plane...
Could they have fallen
out of it?
[ASA] Mm-mm.
They vanished
in midair somehow.
The doors never opened.
We know for a fact
that they boarded in Tokyo.
But when it landed,
they were nowhere to be found.
[YURU] Did someone abduct them?
[ASA] We don't know.
[YURU] Why was
no one guarding them?
[ASA] They had a guard.
The Kagemoris assigned
one of our most trusted
Daemon Wielders
to see they
arrived there safely.
They still disappeared,
guard and all.
[gasps] About that guard...
Think they could have had
something to do with it?
[ASA] Yeah.
It's crossed our minds.
They could've been an enemy,
just playing the part.
Say, an agent
from Higashi Village,
sent to infiltrate
the Kagemoris.
[Yuru grunts]
Regardless of their allegiance,
an apology is in order.
By no means
should we have lost them.
And what? You really
still trust these guys?
They lost our parents!
After we left the village,
their assassins hounded us
day after day
with seemingly no end.
There's one reason
we stayed safe all those years.
It's thanks
to the kindness of Jin
and the Kagemori clan.
[Yuru gasps softly]
So, yes, I trust them
with my life.
[Yuru grunting]
[MAN 1] The boy made his way
inside Kagemori manor.
[WOMAN] Jin managed to work
faster than we expected.
[MAN 1] In 400 years,
they're the first twins
we've seen
born to sunder night and day.
[MAN 2] Four hundred years!
400 years! 400 years!
[MAN 3] They're both down here.
Away from the mountain.
[MAN 1] Our timing
couldn't be better.
The girl with the jaw daemon
is badly injured.
[MAN 3] Jin, too.
[MAN 1] And the master is away.
[MAN 4]
What a golden opportunity.
We can easily seize
both twins at once.
[WOMAN] Easily?
There is still the boy
and his daemons.
They seem quite capable.
[MAN 2] And the girl?
What of the girl?
Don't forget the girl!
[MAN 1] We're striking at night.
She's weaker
than during the day.
The boy is dangerous.
But we're fine to let him die.
As for the girl,
we only need
what's above the neck!
[Right grunts]
♪
[squeaking]
[Gabby groaning]
[GABBY] What?
Why'd you wake me up
before the sun's even out?
♪
[GABBY] Huh?
I don't think we've met before.
[Gabriel growling]
[footsteps running]
So much for being
treated like guests, Jin!
Looks like you led us
straight into a trap!
[JIN] No, those daemons
don't belong
to any of the Kagemoris!
Seems outsiders
have broken into the manor.
[LEFT] Have we leave
to take them down?
I'd like to capture their master
alive for questioning,
if it's at all possible!
How do you propose we do that?
This manor is labyrinthine!
Simply finding them
will prove a trial!
[SAKURAZAWA] If you're going
to fight them, don't go halfway.
Be sure to confirm your kills!
I'll be annoyed if you give me
more people to treat.
You call yourself a doctor,
and you're gonna talk like that?
What happens to a daemon pair
when their master dies?
If they're not transferred
to a new master beforehand,
then they become strays.
That's why,
at least for most of us,
we prioritize our masters!
[all screaming]
So? What happens then?
The daemon's contract
comes to an end,
and they're bound
to that location like a ghost.
If no new contractor appears,
they're likely to be
forgotten over time.
After a few decades
or centuries,
-they usually cease to exist.
-[growling]
That seems too cruel to them.
Understood.
I'll try leaving
their master alive if I can.
You were ready
to kill them outright?
My brother's a saint!
Jin, they have
any bow and arrows?
Well, my boy?
[YURU] What is all that?
You can't just give me
a normal bow?
I suppose
I'll give this one a try.
[both growling]
[Asa gasps]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[Asa gasps] Where's my brother?
[GABBY] You mind if I just
do my thing over here?
[ASA] If my brother
acquires the power of Seal,
she'll be his nemesis, too.